[{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735656973351,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":33100,"timeElapsed":77193},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735656985021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":11660,"timeElapsed":88862},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657002246,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":17217,"timeElapsed":106087},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657020517,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":18267,"timeElapsed":124359},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657031551,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":11029,"timeElapsed":135393},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657045383,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":13827,"timeElapsed":149224},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657061546,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":16155,"timeElapsed":165387},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657069539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7988,"timeElapsed":173381},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657082512,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":12963,"timeElapsed":186354},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657094530,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9859,"timeElapsed":198372},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657098930,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4392,"timeElapsed":202772},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657102748,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3812,"timeElapsed":206590},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657110386,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":7632,"timeElapsed":214228},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657119801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9410,"timeElapsed":223643},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657129919,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":10112,"timeElapsed":233761},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657140575,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":10650,"timeElapsed":244417},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657144471,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3892,"timeElapsed":248313},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657148370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3895,"timeElapsed":252212},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657163317,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":13070,"timeElapsed":267159},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657176144,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":12820,"timeElapsed":279986},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657180571,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4419,"timeElapsed":284413},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657184408,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3831,"timeElapsed":288250},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657188111,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3700,"timeElapsed":291953},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657191681,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3565,"timeElapsed":295522},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657199906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8217,"timeElapsed":303748},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657206446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":6535,"timeElapsed":310287},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657211441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4991,"timeElapsed":315283},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657233239,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":21792,"timeElapsed":337081},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657243771,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8229,"timeElapsed":347613},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657248372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4594,"timeElapsed":352214},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657252809,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4431,"timeElapsed":356651},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657258027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":5212,"timeElapsed":361869},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657262474,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":4441,"timeElapsed":366316},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657266485,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":4004,"timeElapsed":370326},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657272254,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":5761,"timeElapsed":376096},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657276179,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":3918,"timeElapsed":380021},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657279381,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":3198,"timeElapsed":383223},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657291574,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":10006,"timeElapsed":395416},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657297254,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5673,"timeElapsed":401096},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657301604,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":4342,"timeElapsed":405446},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657305926,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":4313,"timeElapsed":409768},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657313826,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":7893,"timeElapsed":417668},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657322276,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":8442,"timeElapsed":426118},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657325651,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":3368,"timeElapsed":429493},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657329760,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":4105,"timeElapsed":433602},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657335606,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":5839,"timeElapsed":439447},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657346273,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9194,"timeElapsed":450115},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657349361,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3079,"timeElapsed":453203},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657352601,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":3234,"timeElapsed":456443},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657356412,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":3806,"timeElapsed":460253},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657362345,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5925,"timeElapsed":466186},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657365699,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":3348,"timeElapsed":469541},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657369586,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3882,"timeElapsed":473428},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657380270,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":10676,"timeElapsed":484112},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657384585,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4310,"timeElapsed":488427},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657402458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":16537,"timeElapsed":506300},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657406018,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3551,"timeElapsed":509860},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657409837,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3815,"timeElapsed":513679},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657413416,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3575,"timeElapsed":517258},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657416417,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2994,"timeElapsed":520259},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657419917,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":3495,"timeElapsed":523759},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657423273,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3352,"timeElapsed":527115},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657428966,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5687,"timeElapsed":532807},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657432861,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3889,"timeElapsed":536703},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657436837,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3967,"timeElapsed":540679},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657450152,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":11604,"timeElapsed":553993},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657453179,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3022,"timeElapsed":557020},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657457307,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4121,"timeElapsed":561149},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657462111,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4799,"timeElapsed":565953},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657465275,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":3160,"timeElapsed":569117},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657469086,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":3807,"timeElapsed":572928},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657472385,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3293,"timeElapsed":576227},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657475298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2907,"timeElapsed":579140},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657478656,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3350,"timeElapsed":582498},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657489188,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8347,"timeElapsed":593030},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657496962,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7769,"timeElapsed":600804},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657501873,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4907,"timeElapsed":605715},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657510177,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":8298,"timeElapsed":614019},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657514113,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":3932,"timeElapsed":617955},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657517682,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":3564,"timeElapsed":621524},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657521542,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3852,"timeElapsed":625384},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657524957,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":3410,"timeElapsed":628798},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657529247,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4285,"timeElapsed":633088},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657541351,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":10133,"timeElapsed":645193},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657544044,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2685,"timeElapsed":647886},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657546532,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2484,"timeElapsed":650374},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657559370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":12831,"timeElapsed":663212},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657563392,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":4015,"timeElapsed":667234},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657566922,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":3524,"timeElapsed":670764},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657570470,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3541,"timeElapsed":674312},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657573926,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3447,"timeElapsed":677767},{"subjectID":"bn5mdvz222","prolificID":"67417406c867bf3694fa2bce","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b32776c921aa20c79b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735657577531,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":3600,"timeElapsed":681373}]